Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous, Approximately 250 items, including certificates awarded to Sanborn; various order forms and applications forms; un-used post cards and greeting cards; membership cards; calling cards; chain letters; a dog tag of Wiley M. Joyner, and a drawing of the Sanborn Family's coat of arms. (Box 37, Box 38, Box 39)
Marti, Fritz, A Philosophical Glossary, Edwards Bros.Inc., Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1933. (Sent to catalog dept.7/8/69 to be cataloged for open stacks)
Sanborn, Herbert Charles, (ed.), Karl Heinrich Erzahlung von Wilhelm Meyer-Forster, Newson and Co., New York 904. (Sent to catalog dept.7/8/69 to be cataloged for open stacks)
Schiller, Friedrich von, Der Neffe Als Onkel, with intorduction, notes, vocabulary, and conversational exercises by Herbert C. Sanborn, Maynard, Merrill and Co., 1906. (Sent to Catalog dept. 7/8/69 to be cataloged for "S" Collection)
Sudermann, Hermann, Teja, with introduction, notes and vocabulary by Herbert C. Sanborn, Henry Holt, New York, 1905. (Sent to catalog dept. to be cataloged for "S" Collection, 7/8/69)
Stearns, Richard G., The Cumberland Plateau Overthrust And Geology Of The Crab Orchard Mountains Area, Tennessee, Nashville, Tenn., 1954. (Sent to catalog dept. 7/8/69 to be cataloged for "S" Collection)
Stroud, Robert, Diseases of Canaries, Canary Publishers Co., Kansas City, Mo., 1933. (Sent to cataloging dept.7/8/69 to be cataloged for "S" Collection)